

(+66) 64-135-1355



thureindev@outlook.com



Bangkok, Thailand



https://thureindev.github.io

THUREIN TUN



W E B DEVELOPER

An enthusiastic builder, learner, and teacher. My strong foundation in computing and business management complements my hands-on experience in web development and teaching.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- ExpressJS
- TypeScript
- Flask
- Python
- Tkinter
- PHP
- MongoDB
- HTML & CSS
- MySQL
- NodeJS
- Postgresql
- React
- Microservices
- Jekyll
- Kubernetes
- Git
- Jenkins
- Docker

PROFILE

I specialize in building web solutions using the **MERN stack**. My background with PHP has equipped me to understand and adapt to diverse coding environments, My proficiency extends to **Python**, particularly for data manipulation and automation.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Visit my portfolio projects at

https://thureindev.github.io

When I'm not busy with freelance work, I like to get hands-on with my own fun projects. Exploring new tech, tackling different challenges, and keeping the learning curve alive and kicking. It's all about pushing the limits and seeing what cool stuff I can create.

EDUCATION

B.A. ENGLISH

Dagon University 2019 Graduated

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

Business Institute Yangon 2019 Graduated

HND IN COMPUTING

GUSTO College

2017 Graduated

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCING

Client Projects and Personal Projects Mar 2022 - present

- This experience sharpened my technical skills.
- I developed my skill on flexible approach to problem-solving.

BASIC PROGRAMMING TUTOR

YIUS - Yangon Institute of University Studies Jan 2020 - Aug 2021

- Taught basic programming concepts to college students
- Prepared class resources and open book knowledge tests.

IOS FRONTEND INTERN

REVOTECH

Jun 2017- Dec 2017

- Using Swift I worked as frontend iOS dev.
- iOS view components in MVC architecture.